const e="apes_rev3",o="Exam Review 3",t=[{question:"Which of the following is the proper order from surface to center of the Earth?",choices:["mantle, crust, outer core, inner core","crust , outer core , inner core, mantle","inner core, outer core, crust, mantle","crust, mantle, outer core, inner core","inner core, outer core, mantle, crust"],number:1,correct:3},{question:"Which contains older rock?",choices:["continental crust","oceanic crust","they are the same in age"],number:2,correct:0},{question:"One tectonic plate may contain",choices:["only oceanic crust","only continental crust","both continental and oceanic crust plus the upper mantle","only one kind of crust and the asthenosphere","crust, upper mantle and asthenosphere"],number:3,correct:2},{question:"What happens at a subduction zone?",choices:["continental plate subducts under oceanic plate","continental plate subducts under continental plate","oceanic plate subducts under oceanic crust","oceanic crust subducts under continental crust","either c or d"],number:4,correct:4},{question:"Which of the following is not commonly associated with tectonic plate boundaries?",choices:["volcanoes","earthquakes","mid-ocean ridges","folded mountain chains","very old rock"],number:5,correct:4},{question:"What kind of rock is formed from weathering, erosion and deposition?",choices:["igneous","metamorphic","sedimentary"],number:6,correct:2},{question:"A mineral that a country uses but does not produce itself is called",choices:["fossil fuel","strategic","reserve","non-fuel","metamorphic"],number:7,correct:1},{question:"Put the following layers of the atmosphere in the proper order",choices:["troposphere mesosphere stratosphere thermosphere","troposphere stratosphere mesosphere thermosphere","stratosphere thermosphere troposphere mesosphere","troposphere mesosphere stratosphere thermosphere","stratosphere thermosphere mesosphere troposphere"],number:8,correct:1},{question:"In which of the above layers does a layer of ozone protect us from UV rays?",choices:["troposphere","thermosphere","mesosphere","stratosphere"],number:9,correct:3},{question:"Which of the following best describes why there are rainforests at the tropics",choices:["warm air rises, cools and condenses into rainclouds","cold air sinks, bringing rain with it","warm air is trapped under cold air, forming clouds","rising cold air hits sinking cold air, resulting in high precipitation","a high pressure system causes water vapor to condense into water droplets"],number:10,correct:0},{question:"Where are you most likely to find deserts?",choices:["at high pressure areas formed by sinking air","at low pressure areas formed by rising air","at high pressure areas formed by rising air","at low pressure areas formed by sinking air"],number:11,correct:0},{question:"At what latitude are deserts most likely to be found?",choices:["0°","30° N or S","60° N or S"],number:12,correct:1},{question:"Which of the following was not a result of El Niño?",choices:["less rain in Indonesia","more rain in South America","stronger equatorial winds blowing currents Westward","less upwelling of nutrient-rich water off the coast of S.A.","higher sea levels along the Western coasts of North and South America"],number:13,correct:2},{question:"Which of the following is not a greenhouse gas?",choices:["CFCs","carbon dioxide","methane","nitrous oxide","SO2"],number:14,correct:4},{question:"Which of the following is not predicted to be an effect of global warming?",choices:["higher sea level","stronger storms","droughts","decreased rate of photosynthesis","migration of species towards the poles"],number:15,correct:3},{question:"Which of the following correctly describes the cause and effect of the Coriolis effect",choices:["cause: rotation of the earth; effect: deflection of winds into gyres","cause: changes in the Earth’s orbit; effect: climate fluctuations","cause: tilt of the earth’s axis; effect: change of seasons","cause: change in distance to sun; effect: change of seasons","cause: presence of mountains; effect: location of deserts on leeward side of mountains"],number:16,correct:0},{question:"Which of the following is not a result of photochemical reactions",choices:["NO2","particulates","PAN","VOC","ozone"],number:17,correct:1},{question:"Which of the following substances is an indoor pollutant linked to lung cancer?",choices:["PAN","O3","freon","SO2","radon"],number:18,correct:4},{question:"Which of the following is least likely to be associated with air pollution?",choices:["bronchitis","cataracts","emphysema","asthma","fibrosis"],number:19,correct:1},{question:"Which of the following reactions is not a significant contributor of acid precipitation?",choices:["H2SO4","HNO3","HCl"],number:20,correct:2},{question:"Where in the United States are you most likely to find acid deposition?",choices:["Northeast","Southwest","Northwest","Southeast","central"],number:21,correct:0},{question:"Which of the following is not an effect of acid precipitation?",choices:["spruce trees lose needles","damage to limestone and marble buildings","heavy metals leached out of the soil","pH of mountain lakes increase dramatically","many fish eggs dies"],number:22,correct:3},{question:"What is best removed by electrostatic precipitators?",choices:["particulates","CO","SO2","limestone","hydrocarbons"],number:23,correct:0},{question:"The east side of Mount Waialeale in Hawaii receives 20x the rain as the west side. What can you infer about Mount Waialeale?",choices:["there is a large lake between the two sides","trade winds blow from East to West across the mountain","the west side is at a different latitude from the east side","the Mountain is subjected to a strong Coriolis effect","the mountain creates a high pressure system on the east side"],number:24,correct:1},{question:"Which of the following is true of most aquifers today?",choices:["recharge is slower than water withdrawal","water table wells are becoming artesian wells","the water table is rising","the rate of infiltration is faster than in the past"],number:25,correct:0},{question:"Which of the following is responsible for the greatest water use?",choices:["agriculture","industry","domestic use"],number:26,correct:0},{question:"Which of the following environmental problems is not related to groundwater depletion.",choices:["saltwater intrusion","land subsidence","sinkholes","cone of depression","siltation"],number:27,correct:4},{question:"What is the effect of adding organic wastes to a river?",choices:["increase of BOD and increase of DO","decrease of BOD and increase of DO","decrease of BOD and decrease of DO","increase of BOD and decrease of DO"],number:28,correct:3},{question:"Eutrophication in a marine ecosystem can cause an increase of toxic dinoflagellates called",choices:["red tide","El Niño","oligotrophic","Minamata disease","turbidity"],number:29,correct:0},{question:"How would a thermal plume affect the DO of an aquatic ecosystem?",choices:["DO would increase","DO would decrease"],number:30,correct:1},{question:"Which of the following has caused the greatest health risk to humans",choices:["human and animal wastes in water","pesticides","air pollution","second-hand smoke","radioactive wastes"],number:31,correct:0},{question:"Which of the following is likely to be found in sludge?",choices:["lead","cadmium","nitrates","phosphates","all of the above"],number:32,correct:4},{question:"What is the purpose of secondary sewage treatment?",choices:["to remove all plant nutrients","to allow anaerobic microorganisms to decompose sludge","to allow aerobic microorganisms to decompose organic matter","to remove all heavy metals","to physically remove grit"],number:33,correct:2},{question:"Which of the following is not an oxygen-demanding waste?",choices:["animal manure","dead algae","dead fish","human sewage","mercury"],number:34,correct:4}],s={id:e,displayName:o,questions:t};export{s as default,o as displayName,e as id,t as questions};
